<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Useless Filter</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.UselessFilter</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/UselessFilter</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]

Setting up filters for what items to destroy by smelting, burning, deconstructing, recycling etc. is always tedious.
I find I often have two or three recipies per bench to match all types of items.
To simplify this, the mod creates a useless and a non-useless filter to the Apparel and the Weapon lists.
The settings lets you define conditions that makes something useless.

Currently it has settings for 
[list]
[*] % Hit points
[*] Quality range
[*] Tainted/clean
[*] Biocoded/non-biocoded
[/list]

If any of the above settings match, it is considered useless. 
If not, its non-useless.

I created this mod mostly to simplify for myself, but hopefully someone else gets use out of it!

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2810866437]Russian translation[/url] by proselyte223 

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/UselessFilter][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/O0IIlYj.png[/img]
Since modding is just a hobby for me I expect no donations to keep modding. If you still want to show your support you can gift me anything from my [url=https://store.steampowered.com/wishlist/id/Mlie]Wishlist[/url] or buy me a cup of tea.

[url=https://ko-fi.com/G2G55DDYD][img]https://i.imgur.com/Utx6OIH.png[/img][/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>